{
    "subject": "resource/Vadim_Pisarev",
    "predicate": "ontology/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Dance",
    "human_readable": "Vadim Pisarev's occupation is Dance.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9329743981361389,
            "question": "Is Vadim Pisarev a dancer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.851044774055481,
            "question": "What is Vadim Pisarev's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7840650677680969,
            "question": "Is dance a part of Vadim Pisarev's daily routine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7496732473373413,
            "question": "Describe Vadim Pisarev's career."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6246346235275269,
            "question": "What is Vadim Pisarev's job title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6170668601989746,
            "question": "What is Vadim Pisarev known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5616335868835449,
            "question": "What type of work does Vadim Pisarev specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40115606784820557,
            "question": "What field does Vadim Pisarev work in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34717902541160583,
            "question": "What does Vadim Pisarev do for a living?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3220667243003845,
            "question": "What kind of art form does Vadim Pisarev practice?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vadim Pisarev's occupation is Dance.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6847_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does Vadim Pisarev do for a living?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6847_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field does Vadim Pisarev work in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6847_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work does Vadim Pisarev specialize in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6847_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6847_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6847_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6847_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6847_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6847_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6847_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6847_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6847_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6847_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6847_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Vadim Pisarev being a famous Ukrainian dancer and detailing his career, which supports the statement that his occupation is dance."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}